What can I tell you? She's a big girl.
(Bernadette:)Wherever you look, there she is.
(Bernadette:)More coffee?
(Penny:)No, Leonard's taking me
to a physics lecture...
...and coffee will just keep me awake.
(Penny:)Oh, I'll get it.
(Amy:)Oh, looks like someone's
on Team Bernadette.
(Amy:)- Where's Howard?
- He's not here. What's wrong?
(Amy:)He had my car towed.
It cost me $200 to get it back.
(Bernadette:)Oh, no.
(Bernadette:)Where was it parked?
(Amy:)In Sheldon's spot.
(Bernadette:)Well, that doesn't make sense.
Sheldon doesn't have a spot.
(Bernadette:)Was it maybe in Howard's spot?
(Amy:)Don't play dumb with me, sister.
You tell your husband he owes me $200.
- Well, that doesn't make sense either.
- Why not?
(Bernadette:)Because I'm the one who had it towed.